Daniel and Breslin attention oh my god
[Music]
sir ah hello dear Sunshine's welcome
back to our YouTube channel in today's
video as you have read on the typo
okay so que con man hmm nice I'm gonna
shine the hell up on a mine
no okay so in today's video as you have
read on the title Gaga be naughty nanny
soon ISA air cushion it's a CC cream
first impression /v so if you want to
know all about this initial water beauty
air pad CC cream please keep on watching
I hope everyone have seen this already
on Facebook know I'm Brendan Shanghai on
this one the Sinisa water beauty and air
pad CC cream I am sure there you are so
I pour she said this on Sharpie the
canopic O'Doyle gone cinnamon be been
finito actually in a message a new Nepal
I'm in manure okay so back on the video
Eponine are trending Shanghai on YouTube
to trending shut my hands of Facebook
top words I can say I asked how much
each M Daniel and by how much
so they messaged me and they're giving
their 50% off they say these costs 2899
like that and there
one three something Nalani on bicep
around to eight and one 399 I am Not
sure pero one three and Sosa become aha
gosh nicosia forward that was in and
pushes a shopping i lucky taco ulna
Nakamura it cost three hundred something
I think 399 or 300 something you Delilah
given along the description box parama
bus anymore
so are you Nagar so Nakamura bar
typically nothing if it's legit if it's
authentic
unknown signal nothing so let's now go
to the product first impression slasher
view that this one this is the Sinisa
water beauty and ear pads CC cream a
young shared on box Nia and look at that
it's I think this is Korean product iron
sha and alum news and a pop on Simcoe
unknown mana laminate an authentic sha a
Chaka Khan fiction KU Molly experience
box or any parts of product Sona God of
akhaten O Muhammad in spelling ha ha ha
ha Moorish I know the hill macapa maraca
Erica CLM no minsang kappa banana piano
Machado mu redundant a NOP bake a fella
Gong mus maganda Telugu mallamma
if legit or authentic you but be behind
a pen but I just wanted to try this one
I think an identical behind a mine
rather than not but we don't know cos a
marijuana replicas na ba ha since nakaka
irritate me in a pen so we don't know so
I in a shiner open parasha if you open
the box it looks like this here is the
question
and mary jean cusamano sponge or blender
let's look at the blender and then the
Shiva Simran shankaranarayana danyoung
and i am sure i
Binion sharp Alafaya it's color black
obviously and I am so now I hope Nikita
animal videos NATO I know angling
minagawa nila so I am sure it's Sinisa
what a beauty and air cushion CC cream
and are you on mine not even a song
wrong spelling keeping you by onion
beautician iron iron Audubon so I hope
still I hope still good the bus I am the
nominee hundred not been so when you
open it it looks like this and I think
this is a mirror we just have to get to
film on it
iron and then a Chaka boom Chaka Neil an
advertisement Makiki that cream
there you are let's look at it who hot
iron on hunting dream at in Allegan
additional they said it has two shades
pero well I don't wanna hung up a
billion a shade I am sure so it looks
like this creamy Shawn Machado and if I
put it like that I'm puttin yakaza
Telugu Hindi Makati and a keen come I so
I think and I hope it's blendable iron I
think be blended in Shawano yen and my
cream Bella gosh it's not bothering Amoy
it's just a typical cream I am I am sure
so they said it close come on
and closed Monday night then and then we
open it fear there you are
and it still has a film so let's see
Caesarea advertisement Nina they just
pressed it baby does it work
or do I have to get oh okay so I have to
get the this one and I ania ania Nikita
and I tons of facebook name Aaron
Ghanaian and then if we press it the
only the bus um cream Lexi
oh I am sure yeah and I Union a Chiquita
and a stance advertisement nila
advertisement iron and then if you use
the sponge or Beauty Blender it creates
a iron
and I so let's put it here depending on
tire you sing at a the blender and then
you blend it
Oh Malik Shah Bank upon a film la
madrina I am sure so yes I think we can
blend it when our skin and they also
said nah waterproof shot iron as you can
see all the bar was magenta pan and
Anita and on blender case a new Suginami
tank Hashanah laughing come I so let's
know about this Sinisa water and by
doing so he's a water beauty an
air-cushion CC cream so it says not it's
a water beauty cushion CC cream its neck
content is 20 grams its shelf life is
three years suitable for all skin types
its efficacy is concealer brighten skin
tone long-lasting moisturizing normal
specification and its air-cushion so now
we are going to try it on our face
alright so let's press it like that part
of the mobis him cream and then I'll get
or hide any magic around on your long
press on that
Oh
[Music]
nothing boo me Lena Oh young man but I
will fix this
mm-hmm all right so let's go back on the
video it's my mistake I said beanie
english' force will EKU inertia balasso
no blossom so I got log notion angle you
can young parent plastic Malala bus and
noon cream so yes well I'm a couple ppl
sat in a going on video NATO hiya subbu
Canon happen I put some of the creams
here cuz I am the man okay so I'll put
it now and we'll see I know it sure on
yeah I am kappa gimmick commitment own
can along beautyblender nap economics of
face and I think I'm Tommy long and the
illigal coal but let's try
so as you can see it a young partner
Neela Bianco obviously at autonomy new
muela identity the usually among Korean
products as in nakaka
and patina that like I usually similar
Korean dreams and put pina wala silang
uparasa
different skin tones but it says not the
lava dome shade Nia pero ella no
incident believe is Athena a sunshade
but knock up a glass skin sha singing an
operon glowing the BA I am a ton of my
new partner it's gonna Milligan codon
Conte actually contain an alum him and
it belongs blender and malaga Cosima - I
am sure can you see that as for I know
you wanna Pat upon Yabba
and blemishes Megan Panama areas Nikita
and Cornyn I think a same Adamiak on red
spots efface the Guyana tall so he
indicia totally in coverage hindi Telugu
gonna knock off a cover but it's really
blendable Casa Colina and pooty pooty
Nia de Bono una cuestión Anila guy but
if you blend the air now I will are you
so Blanc would be non cream and what I
like in this one is glowing sha I
inaudible the baracan nog highlighter
now on this part okay so that opossum
communi on this side and there was let's
see
[Music]
so here it is my dear Sun shines Conte
long talaga in Malaga iconic cream
actually you mama and Vito lungs a
Beautyblender Neela come on along you
and etirsa blender Union elegance of a
school and it's not a really
full-coverage Hindi chiffon foundation
Dana well it's a CC cream but what I
like in this product is my glowing
affection Allen una caja glass kin-yuen
panel including what I don't like in
this product is I think it's too white
on noon
Machado sham okay as you can see I am
new from April 3 Milligan Coconino non
cream which is blendable no man at Shaka
almost closed NASA kulhanek a mocha
auditorium wala which is this epic
television acting cool I am shocked well
Kasim Reed then much important of Mikasa
Kimiko telega mo kako a white child than
my hand tone dancing at maramatanga
holiday some Canadian economy exposures
a sign so we need a legacy larva Iron
Chef hello my dears and science is so
this is what I look like now after I did
my just a simple makeup okay so my final
thoughts about this is Sinisa water
beauty and the air-cushion CC cream okay
so as you can see canina glowing shadow
bono Paula Donovan and claim a Chicana
propaganda so feels neat uncanny long
Beauty Blender cusamano me I don't know
why if it's just because of the cream or
Paragon Carolyn's a beauty blunder when
I set it with a pressed powder no Allahu
pakka glow Vania but in dynamic driving
man okay so I ensure it's not a full
coverage
it's not a full coverage Snapple
consolidation be it's just a normal skin
long new parent pin a petite long talaga
young skin mo banyan Xiang Amina it's
very creamy
maganda you a mini emergence and not
something non-indian bothering I like
the smell of it param pum a leaf namana
foundation okay so more it's just a
usual cream Manila raveena tandon hindi
Malik get a Shaka in building Shah Baba
God it's light weight on your skin
Moroccan well I'm Neela guy in balance
and feels unsure so I think it's nice no
man so yes that's it for today and I'll
be right back later for the wear test
feedback bigger not economical Tanya
mama younger base so I'll be right back
okay so yes hello there sunshine says so
this will be my final thoughts about the
Sinisa air cushion CC cream and the
earthly means by lack now full coverage
jacilla pero as what I can see on my
face hindi siya you full coverage Tina
Paragon funk foundation and since I
spent the whole day with this Sinisa air
cochon
um I've spanned from nine so eleven
twelve one two three four five it's
already 5:00 in the afternoon so seven
hours Kishan Inessa mo kako and tanana
India Koga a nom nom oil up arrow
Marilyn Marilyn
oiliness brewing behind Oh Connie Leung
and since I carry I see the post
mentioned a new new blood young face
Nessa pisco para bellum transfer Sonya
it's just that part of my apartment at
Natanz no Pooh Kunis economica
so melon punch anyone maybe a very thin
layer of the cream surface um
pression and mine if it's worth it okay
no Mancha and well Anna mentioned each
eNOS because they maybe it's not really
a sense because in Mora but such an
element machinima and I think miss
madenda um customary say that is
sunshade major nude or beige in color so
seguro I think West maganda yeah exactly
but as you can see now para una blend
animal new color in yes
satella gong skin tone Co so it's it's
okay if you would like to purchase it
you can check their FB page marentina an
opinion on unison ISA air-cushion cream
or you can also check on shopping
mechanic Malachi oh and if every NASA
shopping news oblivion Bassanio Murayama
reviews of Chaka Khan singer young
Merrill Pina Colada mean sold item guy
said don't open a b-school
oh hey Bashar hindi and marina mama
comments na nice shot
so I think I know man I can use it on a
daily basis home danyoung model young
rock at Longfellow home from party
events occasion hindi siya GaN on GaN
own conduct
alright so meteor sunshine so that's it
for our first impression / review /
wear test of the Sinisa a water beauty
air cushion CC cream Visayan en shaa
verstehen Yolanda in the description and
I will see you again on my next video
bye bye
[Music]
[Applause]